(Leonard:)Civil servants have a documented
propensity to, you know, snap, so...
(Penny:)Okay. Well, thank you again.
(Leonard:)No problem. Bye.
Oh, and bye, bro. Heh.
(Sheldon:)Penny for your thoughts.
- What's the matter?
- No, I'm fine.
(Leonard:)Penny's fine,
the guy she's kissing is really fine.
Kissing? What kind of kissing?
Cheeks, lips, chase, French?
(Leonard:)What is wrong with you?
(Howard:)I'm a romantic.
(Sheldon:)Don't tell me
that your hopeless infatuation...
(Sheldon:)...is devolving into pointless jealousy.
(Leonard:)No, I'm not jealous.
I'm just a little concerned for her.
(Leonard:)Didn't like the look of the guy
she was with.
Because he looks better than you?
(Leonard:)Yeah.
He was kind of dreamy.